[Music]
hello my friend it's me again I know
it's been a very very very long time
since my last video you I am very happy
to be given this opportunity to share my
experience with you all that I have been
selected as one of the lucky testers to
try one of our famous niia products all
thanks to try and N community and I'm
very happy and excited to be part of it
this is the niia bright deodorant day I
have received this last January 29th it
is a rectangular shape and super
lightweight that you can add inside your
handbag wherever you go what I like
about this product is that it's not as
heavy as other deodorants I have tried
and before this I was using Suave with
deodorant but it was only given as a
gift from the US and I was too sad
thinking that I cannot buy it anywhere
in the Philippines it almost smells like
it almost the same powdery but more
florally scent it's gentle to the nose
especially for us ladies what I also
like about this it's not sticky and
stops the smell of sweat and keeps dry
and it doesn't make me feel sweaty at
all during the day I am very happy to
find another favorite and I can see
myself purchasing another one for
personal use would you like to be a star
member and being advocate of triy rebiew
community